[
  {
    "id": "q1",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Which of the following is not right type of Animal Habitat",
    "options": ["Terrestrial", "Aquarium", "Mountainous", "Aquatic","Grasslands"],
    "answer": "Aquarium"
  },
  {
    "id": "q2",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "A habitat helps animals by providing all of below needs except?",
    "options": ["Food", "HotAir", "Shelter", "Water"],
    "answer": "HotAir"
  },
  {
    "id": "q3",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Camels can live without water for many days",
    "options": ["True", "False", "Uncertain"],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "id": "q4",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Which animal does not live in cold weather ?",
    "options": ["Yak", "Polar Bear", "Mountain Goats", "Leopards"],
    "answer": "Leopards"
  },
  {
    "id": "q5",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "The inner portion of camels mount is like ------",
    "options": ["Water", "Rubber", "leather", "Paper"],
    "answer": "leather"
  },
  {
    "id": "q6",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Excess amount of food is stored as fat in camels ____",
    "options": ["Ears", "Stomach", "Skin", "Hump"],
    "answer": "Hump"
  },
  {
    "id": "q7",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Polar regions of earth are extremely ____",
    "options": ["Cold", "Hot", "Rainy", "Sunny"],
    "answer": "Cold"
  },
  {
    "id": "q8",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Polar bear is covered with thick layer",
    "options": ["fat", "skin", "fur", "hair"],
    "answer": "fur"
  },
  {
    "id": "q9",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "In winter Polar bear sleep for _____",
    "options": ["0 hours", "8 hours", "18-20 hours", "20-24 hours"],
    "answer": "18-20 hours"
  },
  {
    "id": "q10",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Polar bear is covered with thick layer",
    "options": ["fat", "skin", "fur", "hair"],
    "answer": "fur"
  },
  {
    "id": "q11",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "____ and  ___ live in mountains",
    "options": ["Goats and Cows", "Cows and Sheep", "Goat Yak", "Yak Bear"],
    "answer": "Goat Yak"
  },
  {
    "id": "q12",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "_____ protect eyes from strong sandy winds in camel",
    "options": ["fat", "eyelashes", "fur", "hair"],
    "answer": "eyelashes"
  },
  {
    "id": "q13",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "_____ protect camel from hot sand",
    "options": ["skin", "tail", "hump", "long legs"],
    "answer": "long legs"
  },
  {
    "id": "q14",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Many plants grow in polar regions",
    "options": ["True", "False", "Uncertain"],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "id": "q15",
    "type": "multiple-choice",
    "question": "Crows are found all over the world because they eat",
    "options": ["milk", "chocolate", "insects", "fish"],
    "answer": "insects"
  }
]
